Good morning, Patrick.
早上好，帕特里克。
Hup! Good morning, SpongeBob!
哈！早上好，海绵宝宝！
Wanna go for a bike ride
through jellyfish fields?
想去骑自行车
穿过水母区？
You bet your square pants
I do!
你打赌你的方裤
我愿意！
Oh, I love bike riding.
哦，我喜欢骑自行车。
I forgot I don't have a bike.
我忘了我没有自行车。
No problem.
I have a spare.
没问题。
我有一个备用的。
Hmm. Uh-oh.
唔。呃哦。
Hold on, it'll just
take me a minute to find it.
坚持住，只会
请花一分钟时间找到它。
Hm!
嗯！
Sorry, Patrick,
I just can't seem to...
对不起，帕特里克，
我只是似乎无法...
Find it.
找到它。
Check out this sweet ride!
看看这个甜蜜的旅程！
Thanks Gare Bear.
谢谢盖尔熊。
Eee!
哎呀！
Come on, SpongeBob!
Follow me!
加油，海绵宝宝！
跟我来！
Oh, yeah. I don't know how
to ride a bike.
哦，是的。我不知道怎么办
骑自行车。
I guess I can't go bike riding
with you, SpongeBob!
我想我不能去骑自行车
和你一起，海绵宝宝！
Now, don't you worry
your pretty, pink, pointy head.
现在，你不用担心
你漂亮的、粉红色的、尖尖的头。
I can teach you how
to be an expert bicyclist.
我可以教你如何
成为一名自行车专家。
Oh, nice!
哦，不错！
I'm gonna be an icicle mist!
我要变成冰柱薄雾！
Lesson one: How to properly
sit on a bike.
第一课：如何正确
坐在自行车上。
Face forward,
面朝前，
arms parallel but loose,
双臂平行但放松，
both feet placed
firmly on the sand.
双脚放置
牢牢地固定在沙子上。
Uh, okay, then.
呃，好吧，那么。
Uh, here I go.
呃，我来了。
Turn around.
回转。
Other side.
对方。
- Uh--
- Ahh!
- 呃--
- 啊！
But not quite.
但也不完全是。
Okay, uh, gettin' there.
好的，呃，到了。
How's this?
这怎么样？
Uh, maybe we need
a more hands-on approach.
呃，也许我们需要
更实际的方法。
Handlebars grasped firmly,
牢牢握住车把，
tushy planted,
feet stable,
郁郁葱葱的种植，
脚稳定，
and ta-da!
还有哒哒！
I did it!
我做到了！
Don't worry, you just need
to get the hang of it.
别担心，你只需要
掌握它的窍门。
Yeah, almost got it.
是的，差不多明白了。
Ah!
啊!
Nearly there.
快到了。
Close.
关闭。
You know, Patrick,
你知道，帕特里克，
I think you have
gravity trouble.
我想你有
重力麻烦。
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
我不知道什么
你说的是。
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Those should keep you upright.
这些应该让你保持直立。
Maybe some training wheels.
也许一些辅助轮。
That'll make you
a little more stable.
这会让你
更稳定一点。
That's what
my psychiatrist says.
就是这样
我的精神科医生说。
Hm. Uh!
嗯。呃！
Yah.
嗯。
Ooh, ah.
哦，啊。
Yow! Uh!
哟！呃！
Haa!
哈！
Whoa!
哇！
Ay!
- Ah! Ehh!
哎呀！
- 啊！呃！
Oyy.
哎呀。
Ohh!
哦！
Hmm. Time to check
under the hood.
唔。检查时间
在引擎盖下。
Whoa, just as I thought.
哇，和我想的一样。
Your brain's a bit unbalanced.
你的脑子有点不平衡。
Doy! Uhh!
多伊！呃！
Ohh. Ohh!
哦。哦！
Ah-whoo-hoo!
啊呼呼！
Now give it a try.
现在尝试一下。
Rah-hoo-hoo!
啊呼呼！
I think someone's
ready to pedal!
我认为某人的
准备好踩踏板了！
I think so, too!
我也这么认为！
Who?
- That's it.
WHO？
- 就是这样。
Now, pedal nice and easy.
现在，轻松轻松地踩踏板。
And don't you let go!
还有你别放手！
Don't worry, buddy. I won't
take my hands off this bike.
别担心，伙计。我不会
把我的手从这辆自行车上拿开。
I promise.
我保证。
I'm doing it!
我正在做！
Hey!
嘿！
Huh?
啊？
I didn't let go!
我没有放手！
Ohh!
哦！
You need something
to help you focus.
你需要一些东西
帮助您集中注意力。
Way ahead of ya.
远远领先于你。
Mmm.
嗯。
Ooh, hello.
哦，你好。
Yeah, it's working, Patrick!
是的，它起作用了，帕特里克！
You're doing great!
- Ohh!
你做得很好！
- 哦！
Huh?
啊？
For now, just observe me.
现在，就观察我吧。
Take a closer look
and see how it's done.
仔细看看
看看它是如何完成的。
Ahh!
啊！
Watch my feet,
and do what I do.
注意我的脚，
做我做的事。
Ooh.
哦。
That's it.
Now you're getting it.
就是这样。
现在你明白了。
Now pedal
just a little bit faster.
现在踏板
只是快一点点。
Faster?
快点？
Oh, ohh.
哦，哦。
Oh, a little too fast there, Patrick.
哦，有点太快了，帕特里克。
Just relax.
放松点。
I'm relaxed!
我轻松了！
I'm so happy
我太高兴了
we have some time
to ourselves, Puffykins.
我们有一些时间
对我们自己来说，普菲金斯。
Without any interruptions
from--
没有任何打扰
来自——
Look out!
当心！
Sponge!
海绵！
Bob!
鲍勃！
What in the name
名字里有什么
of all that's salty
are you two dipsy doodles--
所有咸的东西
你们是两个迪普西涂鸦吗——
- Squidward.
- What?
- 章鱼哥。
- 什么？
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
♪ La da dee
la da dum ♪
♪ 拉达迪
拉达杜姆 ♪
Of course.
当然。
Ahh!
啊！
Hi, Mrs. Puff.
嗨，普芙女士。
Hello, SpongeBob.
你好，海绵宝宝。
You know, I'm having
a little trouble
你知道，我有
有点麻烦
trying to teach Patrick
how to ride a bicycle.
试图教导帕特里克
如何骑自行车。
Have you ever had trouble
teaching a student, Mrs. Puff?
你有遇到过麻烦吗
泡芙女士，教学生吗？
Ehh.
呃。
Some people are just unteachable.
有些人就是不可教。
Unteachable?
不可教？
Unteach!
That's it!
不教！
就是这样！
Thanks, Mrs. Puff!
谢谢，泡芙女士！
We're having our next date
at home.
我们即将迎来下一次约会
在家里。
You know what
your problem is, Patrick?
你知道吗
你的问题是，帕特里克？
Your brain is just too full
of unimportant knowledge.
你的大脑太满了
不重要的知识。
Yeah, it is pretty
jam-packed.
是的，很漂亮
挤满了人。
Or is it packed with jam?
或者里面塞满了果酱？
We need to make some room
in your head for bike riding.
我们需要腾出一些空间
在你的脑海里骑自行车。
Let's see. Do you remember
how to brush your teeth?
让我们来看看。你还记得吗
如何刷牙？
Of course.
当然。
I even know how
to comb my teeth.
我什至知道如何
梳理我的牙齿。
Uh!
呃！
Well, now you don't.
好吧，现在你不知道了。
Whoo-hoo! Uh!
呼呼！呃！
How to watch TV?
Nah, not important.
如何看电视？
不，不重要。
Dah!
呸！
Put on your pants?
Overrated.
穿上裤子吗？
被高估了。
- Uh!
- Family? Ehh.
- 呃！
- 家庭？呃。
Unnecessary.
不必要。
Uhh--
呃——
Patrick, what is your name?
帕特里克，你叫什么名字？
Who is I?
我是谁？
Ooh, I think someone's
finally ready
哦，我想有人
终于准备好了
to ride a bicycle!
骑自行车！
All right, Patrick,
you're ready.
好吧，帕特里克，
你准备好了。
There's just one more thing
to remember--
还有一件事
记住——
have fun.
玩得开心。
I have no knowledge
of bike riding.
我没有知识
骑自行车的。
Huh? Patrick, get off
that bike before it's too late!
啊？帕特里克，下车
那辆自行车在为时已晚之前！
Don't worry, SpongeBob.
别担心，海绵宝宝。
It's just Bread Man's Hill.
这只是面包人山。
That's not Bread Man's Hill,
那不是面包人山，
it's Dead Man's Hill!
这是死人岭！
Wha--is that worse?
什——那更糟糕吗？
It sounds worse.
听起来更糟。
It is worse!
更糟糕的是！
Ohh no!
哦不！
Whoa!
哇！
Yah!
啊！
Huh. Whoa!
呵呵。哇！
SpongeBob, I'm doing it!
海绵宝宝，我来了！
I'm bicycling!
我骑自行车！
Ahh!
啊！
Uh!
呃！
In honor of becoming
the greatest bicyclist
为了纪念成为
最伟大的自行车手
who has ever lived,
I present you the key
谁曾活过，
我给你钥匙
to Bikini Bottom.
- Ah.
到比基尼底部。
- 啊。
Oh, and the lock!
哦，还有锁！
Patrick! Patrick! Patrick!
帕特里克！帕特里克！帕特里克！
Patrick! Patrick!
帕特里克！帕特里克！
Patrick?
帕特里克？
Oh, thank Neptune
you're okay.
哦，谢谢海王星
你没事吧。
Of course I'm okay.
我当然没问题。
I'm an expert bicyclist now.
我现在是一名自行车专家了。
Patrick, you crashed all
the way down Dead Man's Hill.
帕特里克，你让一切都崩溃了
下死人山的路。
Hmm.
唔。
You've been in a coma
for six weeks.
你一直处于昏迷状态
六个星期。
Whoa!
哇！
A new personal best.
新的个人最好成绩。
Sorry I couldn't teach you
how to ride a bike, Patrick.
抱歉没能教你
如何骑自行车，帕特里克。
Who needs a dumb bike?
谁需要一辆笨自行车？
I am a bike!
我是自行车！
Hop on, buddy!
跳吧，伙计！
Let's roll!
让我们滚吧！
Whee!
哎哟！
Ohh!
哦！
Ahh!
啊！
- Ahh--
- Look out!
- 啊啊--
- 小心！
both: Whoo!
两人：哇！
Huh. I don't know how
to ride a Patrick.
呵呵。我不知道怎么办
骑帕特里克。